Hello, I'm Mahendra.  I am 57 years old.
[music] I have been an FD customer
for more than 10 years
.  Because I got a
pretty good bfed from FD Insurance, especially
the communications carried out
by FD, including agents who always
communicate with me every month
even though I don't claim
the insurance.  [music]
I got the information about the FWD
Care Recovery Plan service from the
[music] email that is always sent every
month and also from Mrs.
Lim's agent.
My FD story.  I am a cancer sufferer
and of course the service from the FWD Care
Recovery Plan Program is very good in
my opinion because at that time [music] I
immediately got facilities from
FWD to [music]
consult with a nutritionist and
psychiatrist, psychologist and also a
physiotherapist.  Well, that really
helped me a lot in recovering
from this illness.
[music]
With the FD Care Recovery Plan that I
got, namely by consulting a
nutritionist, it will improve
my diet and include [music]
better nutrition.  and also I
consulted a psychiatrist and
psychologist because I was experiencing depression,
of course that would improve
my depression and my sleep pattern [music]
well and including doing
physiotherapy [music] that I did,
it would reduce the pain in
my head and neck because of the effects of the
therapy that I had been doing so far.
From what I experienced, the agent Mrs. Lim
who handled my [music] was very good,
especially the information she
provided so far.  Even though I am
not sick, I am always asked how I am and
so on so that all the information from the
FD programs is clearly visible
to me.
So, what I have experienced is the program
from [music] FWD Insurance, especially the FWD
Care Recovery Plan, which has been very good and has
certainly helped me a lot during
this time.  I hope that FWD will come up with many
program innovations that
will be more helpful to its clients.
Not only should there be a care recovery plan in
the form of post-therapy, there should also be something
called a pre-recovery plan.
[music]
that preapi